So what I want is a mother, after all, of course, emo.
Like this already.
I want you to be like, "Wow!" and I want you to be like, "Skin, skin, skin. Really? Oh, skin.
I don't know, but I think she was listening to it. Yes, that's right.
Well, well, well, well. Well then, if you have any requests, please continue to send them to us.
So, that's it for today's program.
See you later!
Thank you very much!
At this point in time, the live YouTube stream is already playing.
Yay! Good evening!
Good evening, I'm Mirei!
Good evening, Devil!
Let's go, Kinch!
Yes!
Good night!
What are you guys doing today? I'm on the radio right now.
What did you guys do? I wonder what they were doing.
I'm tired from work, school, and my part-time job.
Today I'm Sunrai Devil.
Two weeks in a row.
I didn't think it was two weeks in a row.
Yes, I did.
I hope it won't be another three months.
What did you do yesterday?
Yesterday...
What did I do yesterday?
Yesterday?
I saw twins yesterday.
Why?
I was filming.
TikTok.
You go all the way out for a TikTok shoot?
Of course I do.
I shoot for TikTok almost every day.
That's how much TikTok has grown.
So it's better to shoot outside?
Yes, it is.
It's more beautiful in natural light.
That's what they say.
Why don't you try TikTok for the first time?
Is there sound in the video?
Yes, it is.
Good, I'll be sad if I talk alone.
TikTok is playing, too, and I went out and I said, "Yay for the sun!
Yay for the sun!
I'm glad you liked that picture.
I'll have to do it first.
Yay for the sun!
Yay for the sun.
Thank you, sunshine.
Is everything okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Masks, please.
I'm sorry I'm a little late with the show, so I'm going to do a little bit of a screener today.
Oh! It's really good.
I opened this last week.
He's in a hurry.
I'm in a hurry.
But I'm always late with my delivery.
My delivery.
Is this thing on?
Thank you very much.
Oh, ckets!
I love you
what?
Japan
I've changed
I'm drunk
tokumo
Quick!
Are you waiting? Thank you very much. I'll wait for you today too.
Thank you again for your patience today.
I'm going to throw out a star for this week's shift as I did last week.
Two weeks in a row. I'm so happy.
So, let's start the program.
Let's close the show and start the opening.
What's this, like a high-five? What was it?
Didn't we do that? Did we do it?
I don't know...
I don't know, but...
So, here we are again with another memorable moment.
Kimmermaster.
I forgot.
The YT Devil.
1500th today.
1500? Thank you very much.
1,500 times. That's great. 1,500 times?
The other day, it was 1,000... and then there was 500...
So you've been doing this for 1,500 days.
That's great. 500 times.
Well, today, let's talk about 1500, which is the number of times.
Good girl day. Good girl, good girl.
But I'll be a good girl. It's a good girl's day.
If you had 1,500 yen, what would you buy?
That's a good question.
Let me think about it. No, no, no, answer right away.
I'd buy something unexpected... if I had 1,500 yen... unexpectedly...
If I had 1,500 yen, I'd probably go to a sauna.If I had 1,500 yen, I'd probably go to a sauna.
You can go to a sauna for that?
You can go to the sauna. Yes, you can.
I had an image of it costing 4,500 yen.
It's about the same at a proper spa, but at a regular bathhouse, even 1,500 yen is a bit expensive.
Yes, it's a bit cheaper at a super sento.
I see.
If I had 1,500 yen, I'd go to a ramen shop I usually go to, and I'd order their special ramen, plus gyoza (Chinese dumplings).
That would probably be, say, about 1,500 yen for all of it plus gyoza.
You earn 3 points for Nakamoto. One point for every 500 yen.
I've already accumulated a lot. How many points do you have? How many points do you have now? 80.
Can I buy a T-shirt or something? That's right.
I'll wear the T-shirt when I get it. I don't mind if you wear it, but I've never seen anyone wearing it.
I've never seen anyone wearing that. It's like a Nakamoto T-shirt, right?
If I had $1,500, I'd run out of eyeliner right now. Eyeliner is about $1,500.
I want it now!
We don't know what cosmetics are, but they're expensive.
So the most shocking thing to lose might be a pouch.
A cosmetic pouch? Makeup pouch.
So, how many minutes and seconds did you run in the 1,500 meters?
I didn't run 1500m. I used to run 1500m in high school.
I can only run 40 meters. 40 meters?
I'm missing 10 more meters. This is a school site convenience, right?
I can only run 40 meters at an angle.
You can run 1.5 km? Yes, yes, about... 5'30", 5'40", I think.
Isn't that fast? That sounds pretty fast.
I played soccer back then. 1.5 km.
How fast was 1.5 km? I don't know.
You're not running? 1500cc is 1.5 liters, right?
They are often sold in plastic bottles, right? 1.5 liters, 2.5 liters...
I'm drinking 15001.5 liters of water right now.
1500. Wait a minute.
1500... something... 1500... 1500...
1500 is difficult... Oh, by the way, the little Marco cartoon...
I heard it reached 1,500 episodes last year... so I'm about the same age as Chibi Marco?
Yeah, we're about the same.
Chibi Maruko-chan does it once a week, so we're living five times faster.
You're even faster than Chibi Maruko-chan.
It's been around for a long time... maybe since the 1980s...
Maybe it started in the 1980's...
Sazae-san...
If it's her actual age, I mean, she's 24.
She's 24, right? She doesn't age.
Crayon Shin-chan is 3 years old for life.
Amazing, isn't it?
That's why it's been 1,500 times.
I'm truly grateful to all of you.
It's thanks to all of you, and the next is thanks to me.
The next one is thanks to me.
After that, it's all thanks to you, the staff.
Wait, wait, wait. That's not the best thing to say.
I don't like it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God!
I'm like a black-hearted character.
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here.
It's true, the heart is black, too.
It's got a black look to it
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, it's true... so please keep up the good work.
So, without further ado, let's hear from all of you.
Let's see what you have to say.
First of all
The very same Shirinu from Mishima City, Shizuoka Prefecture.
Mr. Shirinu from Mishima City, Shizuoka Prefecture drew this picture!
drew this picture for us!
Thank you very much!
Good evening, Master Sarpon Ejipichu!
Good evening, Deborah!
Congratulations on your 1500th broadcast!
Thank you very much.
A lot of things have happened.
I hope that this program will continue for many more years to come.
That's why I've been drawing this picture!
Wow!
Congratulations!
It's just the beginning.
It's just the beginning!
It's so cute!
Fifteen hundred.
You're really good at drawing, aren't you?
You're so good!
So, if there's going to be another celebration like this, it's going to be 2000, isn't it?
2000, right?
500 more, right?
500 more times!
After 100 rounds, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
Next year.
Yeah, yeah.
Two more years.
Two years.
Two years
I think it's a little less than two years.
That's a long time to wait.
Until then.
Less than two years.
Until then, you all have to wait.
Me, too.I'm the same way.
Please let me work here forever.
Please let me work here.
Chihiro.
There's two of us.
I'll do anything.
This is Chihiro.
That's me.
Yes, it's me.
It's me.
She says it's me.
She said it's me.
It wasn't Chihiro.
Ubaba is at a loss...
It's me, she says.
Well, well, well... Thank you very much.
Now then...
Now, from now on...
I'll take a picture of you two, too.
Yes.
They're sending them to me.
Then, what do you want first?
Yes.
My latest food obsession.
This way, this way.
From this way.
This way first.
Here you go.
This is chukumi.
There it is!
I heard from Mayamaama the other day.
That's right.
She told me because she wanted it.
And this is a picture of you and Maya.
I see.
This is...
This is it.
I heard that, and Sarfon was eating there, too.
Maya recommended it to me when she came as a guest.
He recommended it to me, so I went there right away.
It's not so bad!
It was really good.
But I went to eat alone.
What?
This is for two people only!
That's right, two servings. I grabbed the bug by myself.
Mooooo!
He's such a good boy!
He's a good boy.
She's praising herself now.
I have a lot of questions... about a lot of things.
Like the bento and...
Here.
Yes, yes, I'll eat it.
You'll eat it, won't you?
Yes, yes, yes.
Before the lunch...
If you eat the food that comes out...
I'm full.
Yes.
So he said, "No, thank you for the bento.
I'll eat both.
Because it's bad for the staff.
He'll eat his lunch, too.
He's a good boy.
It was really delicious.
How was it?
It was good.
Well...
How was it?
I don't know.
What is it?
Hey.
Why are you sleeping?
No, no, no.
Why are you...
Oh, no.
Is that it?
I don't know...
Good guys...
We'll do our best.
No, no, no.
I'm a little skeptical about "good guys
Why?
It can't be true.
How many good guys are there in front of us?
That's right, that's right.
Because they're all like that.
Oh, no!
Here's the Aliquot.
Ah!
There or there?
And the scene of the live broadcast.
That's right.
Oh, yeah.
I just ate.
It's like this.
It's so good!
Oh, wow.Uh...
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
I always add shrimp as a topping. It doesn't have shrimp in it to begin with, but it tastes so good topped with shrimp.
I'll try it again next time.
UFO is coming through. See?
It's a child.
Here we go.
And Almani fried rice.
What's that?
Tsukumi,
What is this?
It's fried rice with the sauce after the tsukumi, it's called "Armani Fried Rice".
Eeeeee, that's so cool! I love that kind of thing!
I love that kind of thing!
It's so delicious, and when you're done eating it all, you take it out and put the ingredients back in.
Then you actually make fried rice like this.
Then, I put Korean seaweed and tobiko on top of it, and it's really delicious.
I don't know the name of this one, by the way. I don't know what it's called.
Armani fried rice.
Armani" means "tobiko" or "egg,
It's full of "mani"?
Armani Fried Rice.
Is this salmon aggregate okay?
It's fine. I'm looking at it in the talk section.
I was told this by the restaurant staff.
Do you want fried rice? But I'm alone!
But I was alone!
I thought I would never be able to eat it. I couldn't eat it, but I should have.
I should have eaten it.
Please go with the members.
Yes, I would like to go with Shingo. I would like to go with Shingo.
Armani fried rice.
It's super delicious!
No, of course it's delicious!
It's a little spicy.
It's so good with cheese and other toppings.
It's like I'm eating it for this.
I'd say it's more like this.
I'm eating it for the sake of it.
So it's that good.
Because I'm eating it for the nabe (hot pot) and the udon noodles in the shishibe (rice bowl).
Or zosui (rice porridge).
I can't get enough of it.
Yes, yes, yes.
And what a surprise.
There's a picture from Surfbon too.
Wait a minute.
What's that? Where did this go?
Where did it go?
Wait a minute.
It's supposed to be in here.
Yes, sir.
Let's see.
Wait a minute.
Have you seen it?
I've seen it. I've seen this too.
Wait a minute.
Well, well, well... it's around here somewhere.
Yes, it is.
Oh, there it is.
This is it, isn't it?
It's probably around here somewhere.
Do you have it?
Well, there are three of them, by the way.
Did I send you three?
Which one should I choose? I'll take this one.
First of all, this one.
I was wondering...
Do you ever have trouble sleeping?
I don't.
Almost every day.
You give it to her on the bullet train?
Yes, I've been having trouble sleeping lately.
I've been having a hard time sleeping.
That's not good.
I was talking about it to my partner Shingo.
Then Shingo was kind of indifferent.
I heard that this is very good, so he bought it for me.
Nitmin Ear Relaxation Time
The kind you put in your ears like this?
Yes, it's like an earplug with a little hole in it.
You put a little Hokkaido-like thing in there.
Warm?
Yes, it makes your ears warm.
I put these on just today, or yesterday.
I put it on before I went to bed.
Usually it takes me so long to fall asleep.
It's like spinal fluid in my ears.
I get it done when I go for a biopsy or something.
I'm starting to relax a little bit into the spinal fluid.
I can just put my hand in there like this for a little bit.
It changes the flow of the spinal fluid.
It's supposed to help you get a good night's sleep.
I see.
If you're having trouble sleeping
I recommend it.
I highly recommend it.
Even for Shinkansen passengers.
I heard it's like this.It seems to be like this
UFO
Child
I really recommend this!
I like it.
I like the ear thing. I like the ear thing.
I've been feeling a little uneasy about my ears lately.
I want to do a lot of things to warm them up.
And...
You want this one?
I'll take that one.
There it is!
That's it.
We shoot TikTok every day.
We're filming this...
Gourmet food in Harajuku.
Like a gourmet trip.
This is a 52cm
It's called a Tornado Potato.
It's a single potato that's stretched to the limit
and fry it all up.
I think it's Harajuku Junior High School.
I used to go to Harajuku Junior High School when I was in high school.
I used to go there all the time when I was in middle school.
I haven't been there for a long time.
It's changed so much.
It's been a long time since I've been there, and it's changed so much.
And the food scene has developed a lot.
And I enjoyed it a lot.
I see.
It's been a while since I've been there.
Naka-kun, I'd like you to go with me.
I invited him to an exhibition.
I'm going alone.
He asked me to go with him.
We went shopping together in Harajuku.
The way he talks is so similar.
This is enough to pass the mimicry test.
You're right.
I was so surprised when I went there.
You've changed so much.
I don't know...
I don't know if I like the way it was or the way it is now, but...
something
The atmosphere has changed.
It used to be a lot more exciting, didn't it?
It's a little more fashionable.
There's a lot of fashion.
The building is amazing.
It's so much fun.
It's almost like a holiday.
This is...
Shingo.
These two love each other.
Yes, they do.
They're so close, they sleep in the same bed.
Yes, yes.
And...
And this one...
And there you go.
Are they marshmallows?
The ones you bake?
That's right.
Nakajima... regularly...
He eats outside.
We have a culture of eating in the garden.
We have a culture of eating outside.
It's usually the mother who starts it.
"Suddenly we want to barbecue!
And the father
says, "Yes!
And he brings the food.
Craftsman?
He becomes a master charcoal maker.
And then the three of us...
We'll barbecue.
Roasted marshmallows.
Alfort.
Two marshmallows between two marshmallows.
like s'mores.
Nakajima family's annual
Barbecue
A barbecue that starts with Alfort.
I can't believe they roasted marshmallows.
I've had them before.
I went camping with my sister for the first time.
This.
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing, isn't it?
The texture is better than I expected.
I don't know.
It's like a halibut draw.
It's like it's better grilled than eaten plain.
It's like it tastes even better.
It was delicious.It was delicious.
Wow, the Nakajima family...
They're so active.
Amazing.
Actually, I don't know.
But they're well-positioned.
Like there's more to it than meets the eye.
They're too close.
They're so close.
Dad, mom, and brother...
They're all nyah nyah nyah nyah
In town or out on the town
I remember once they came to peek at us...
We're a strange family.
But yes... you and your father...
I went to Univa with my dad...
Or to Disneyland with your mother.
Daughters understand...
What about sons?
I totally go.
He was about 20 years old.
Your mom's a little...
Shut the fuck up and don't talk to him!
There was a time...
There was a moment.
It wasn't awkward.
It was embarrassing.
Like, I couldn't really talk to him.
But basically
I was embarrassed.
Even after I turned 20, I still wanted to go to Disney on my birthday.
I said I wanted to go to Disney on my birthday.
So I said, "Let's go together.
Going to Disney with your mom on your birthday. That's so cute.
What's that?
Is this a real story?
You can write all this down at the bottom of the Comedy Ledge.
Please don't write that.
I had nothing to do with this.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, well, well, well, well, that's why
We're almost done with the live broadcast.
Almost done?
Devil's Charge is coming in like crazy.
What? Why?
Fifteen hundred.
Thank you very much.
We'll each get 15 million yen.
That's a lot.
Congratulations, Mr. Devilch!
From Sagamihara today.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Devilchick.
I'd like to say more, but
I'm sorry, I can't go back.
Thank you so much.
All I can think about is going to Disney with my mom.
No, no, no, no.
All I think about is going to Disney with my mom.
Yes, yes, yes.
So...
I just got a proposal.
It's been a while since we've had squash time.
I know... we've been waiting a while.
That's right.
Then I'll do the pose I learned from you earlier.
I like it.
That's good.
I'll do my own.
Here.
This one, then.
That's good.
Go harden it, neck.
Go ahead and harden it.
This one goes like this, and this one goes like this, and this one goes like this.
Ai!
Yes!
How are you today?
How's today?
Next, Hoshino.
That's nice.
Yes, that's good. So, from here?
Whoo!
Yes.
You too?
Oh, it's all pretty natural, isn't it?
TikTok, huh?
I see.
I've been watching TikTok.
You're going to Disneyland with your mom, right?
That's natural.
I want you to dance this with your mom.
Does my mom dance like a normal person?
I told her to do it.
Mom doesn't dance, she likes to improvise.
What?
Maybe it's the same with Oshiro-san.
What? What's that? Just ask her something.What? What's that? Ask me something and appropriate it.
They sing a really silly song.
She sings using the name of her dog.
I think your mother's an adult.
She is an adult.
And then she makes up her own songs and laughs at herself.
Sometimes during a conversation.
That's terrifying. I'd like to meet her once.
By all means.
Yes, yes, yes. That's why.
You too, Tamamin.
Thank you, Tamamin.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, Kai-san.
Congratulations on your 1500th entry.
Thank you very much.
That's all I have to say,
I'll see you next week for the live delivery.
Thank you very much for this week.
Thank you very much.